<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-04-01T17:02:59+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">magmo</title><subtitle>We build state channels</subtitle><entry><title type="html">mermaid_test</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/04/01/mermaid.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="mermaid_test" /><published>2019-04-01T12:23:00+01:00</published><updated>2019-04-01T12:23:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/04/01/mermaid</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/04/01/mermaid.html">&lt;p&gt;A mermaid diagram:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;mermaid&quot;&gt;
graph TD;
    A--&amp;gt;B;
    A--&amp;gt;C;
    B--&amp;gt;D;
    C--&amp;gt;D;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>George Knee</name></author><summary type="html">A mermaid diagram:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Introducing our second state channel app</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/state-channels/2019/02/12/ttt-launch.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Introducing our second state channel app" /><published>2019-02-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-02-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/state-channels/2019/02/12/ttt-launch</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/state-channels/2019/02/12/ttt-launch.html">&lt;p&gt;In November of last year we launched Rock Paper Scissors, the first application built on the ForceMove state channel protocol. Today we are happy to launch our second such application: Tic Tac Toe!
Here at Magmo, we are working towards our goal of building state channel networks, where users can interact off-chain with security — but with minimal cost and latency. To stress-test our protocols and other software, we build applications that utilize them: for example, games. The process of building the application, as well as feedback we get from gamers and devs, is a great opportunity to learn how we could be doing things differently or better.
Tic Tac Toe is live on the Ropsten testnet, and you can play against a friend or one of our bots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check it out at ttt.magmo.com
Our apps are fully open-source on GitHub and licensed under the MIT license.
If you play either of our games you will also interact with our newly improved channel wallet. Previously integrated into each app itself, the wallet is now a standalone package taking responsibility for signing state updates and blockchain transactions.
If you have any questions or feedback, please come find us in our Discord group!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/ttt.png&quot; alt=&quot;Tic Tac Toe&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">In November of last year we launched Rock Paper Scissors, the first application built on the ForceMove state channel protocol. Today we are happy to launch our second such application: Tic Tac Toe! Here at Magmo, we are working towards our goal of building state channel networks, where users can interact off-chain with security — but with minimal cost and latency. To stress-test our protocols and other software, we build applications that utilize them: for example, games. The process of building the application, as well as feedback we get from gamers and devs, is a great opportunity to learn how we could be doing things differently or better. Tic Tac Toe is live on the Ropsten testnet, and you can play against a friend or one of our bots.</summary></entry></feed>